MIKAELLA PICONES

WEB DEVELOPER & APP SUPPORT ANALYST

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a dedicated web developer who also worked on application support with 2 plus years of experience with the ability to take responsibility for implementing and completing complex assignments. Willing to learn, highly organized with attention to detail and a great track record of managing multiple priorities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accenture Inc.

Java Bootcamp | Aug 2018 - Oct 2018 Project ASM-R | Oct 2018 - Current

- Fixed bugs and developed multiple enhancements for our client's web application eliminating the need for change requests for reduced request turn-around time using Java, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, jQueryUI, JSP, Javascript
- Supported multiple applications within the project via troubleshooting, analyzing, investigating and resolving issues raised by our client through coordinating with multiple teams & including the client as needed.
- Created functional and technical documentations

Web Development Intern

Fortcode Inc. | Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

 Developed an employee time management web application using NodeJS, Express, VueJS, HTML (Pug), PostgreSQL, Git and created unit tests with Mocha and Istanbul through Agile (Scrum)

Freelance

Champion Marketing | Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

 Developed an online ordering system to automate the client's business process using PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Lady Mediatrix Institute

Elementary to High School | 2005 - 2014

• Graduated in Year 2014

University of Santo Tomas

BS Computer Science | 2014 - 2018

- Major in Game Development
- Two-time Dean's Lister

CONTACT ME AT

- Home Address: 406 Highway View, Masin Sur, Candelaria, Ouezon
- mikaellaspicones@gmail.com
- mikpicones.github.io/portfolio
- in /mikaella-picones-4972b9144
- +63 998 359 0911

SKILLS SUMMARY

Front-end Development (HTML, CSS, SASS, Pug, jQueryUI, JSP,ReactJS, VueJS)

Back-end Development (Java, NodeJS, PHP, Python)

Design Frameworks (Material-UI, Bootstrap)

RDBMS (MySQL, PostgreSQL)

Versioning Control (Git, SVN)

Agile Methodology (Scrum)

Adobe Photoshop

IDE (Eclipse, Visual Studio)